RG 062:114, Town of Preston
Preston Records, Inventory of Town of
- Series 9. Election Records, 1818-1935
  - Election returns, 1832-1930 (Box 16, Folder 4-10)
  - Expense reports, 1905-1908 (Box 16, Folder 11-20)
  - Papers, 1832-1934, undated (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
  - Record of applicants for admission as voters, 1899-1906
    See Volumes.
  - Registrar, certification of age, 1872-1873 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Register opf women voters, 1893-1897
  - Town officers
  - Voter lists, 1883-1884 (Box 16, Folder 25-26)
  - Voter lists, 1885-1900 (Box 17, Folder 1-13)
- Series 10. Tax Records, 1794-1932
  - Assessor's books (Box 18)
    - Highway taxes, 1880-1902 (Box 18)
    - School district tax abstracts, 1896-1932 (Box 19)
  - Grand lists
  - List book, 1801-1810 (Box Item 20)
  - List of taxable property
  - Bank stockholders, 1885-1899, undated (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Collector's accounts, 1891-1913 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Town rates, fragments, 1812-1852 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lists, 1819-1896 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Lists, 1891-1894 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Papers, 1794-1925 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Polls and taxable property, 1848
  - School districts, 1849, 1856 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Tax abstracts, 1881-1915
  - Town rates, 1799-1848 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Wagon ownership, 1903 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
- Oversize
  - Series 1: Proclamations, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Series 4: County Commissioners, liqour licenses, 1881-1907 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Series 7: Enumeration forms, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Series 7: 2nd School District, treasurer accounts, 1816-1853 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Series 9: Election notice, 1893 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Expense reports, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Series 9: Town officers, 1878-1893, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Series 9: Voter lists, 1884, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Series 10: List of property, 1875 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Volumes
  Tax abstracts for years 1881 to 1915 are boxed. All other volumes listed here are not. Tax abstracts for the years 1916 to 1930 are stamped "Grand List" on the cover.
  - Series 1: Treasurer accounts, 1862-1897; 1 volume
  - Series 1: Treasurer accounts, 1913-1928; 1 volume
  - Series 9: Register of women voters, 1893-1897; 1 volume
  - Series 9: Record of applicants for admission as voters, 1899-1906; 1 volume
  - Series 10: Polls and taxable property, 1848; 1 volume
  - Series 10: Tax abstracts, 1881-1898, 1900-1930
    - 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 2 volumes for 1882 (Box 24)
    - 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box 25)
    - 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894 (Box 26)
    - 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898 (Box 27)
    - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904 (Box 28)
    - 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909 (Box 29)
    - 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915 (Box 30)
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
    - 1921, 1 volume
    - 1922, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1925, 1 volume
    - 1926, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume
    - 1929, 1 volume
    - 1930, 1 volume